const level10questions = [
  {
    "question": "70 + 92 = ?",
    "options": ["170", "172", "162", "178"],
    "answer": "162"
  },
  {
    "question": "47 + 94 = ?",
    "options": ["141", "123", "131", "150"],
    "answer": "141"
  },
  {
    "question": "42 + 52 = ?",
    "options": ["81", "94", "93", "83"],
    "answer": "94"
  },
  {
    "question": "98 + 74 = ?",
    "options": ["172", "181", "182", "164"],
    "answer": "172"
  },
  {
    "question": "28 + 28 = ?",
    "options": ["59", "71", "74", "56"],
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "50 + 70 = ?",
    "options": ["111", "120", "139", "102"],
    "answer": "120"
  },
  {
    "question": "68 + 60 = ?",
    "options": ["146", "115", "128", "122"],
    "answer": "128"
  },
  {
    "question": "30 + 26 = ?",
    "options": ["56", "73", "45", "68"],
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "42 + 20 = ?",
    "options": ["49", "50", "62", "82"],
    "answer": "62"
  },
  {
    "question": "75 + 75 = ?",
    "options": ["138", "150", "165", "145"],
    "answer": "150"
  },
  {
    "question": "50 + 71 = ?",
    "options": ["110", "114", "121", "103"],
    "answer": "121"
  },
  {
    "question": "72 + 40 = ?",
    "options": ["104", "112", "106", "115"],
    "answer": "112"
  },
  {
    "question": "97 + 19 = ?",
    "options": ["136", "127", "119", "116"],
    "answer": "116"
  },
  {
    "question": "94 + 67 = ?",
    "options": ["161", "147", "176", "174"],
    "answer": "161"
  },
  {
    "question": "53 + 43 = ?",
    "options": ["79", "108", "112", "96"],
    "answer": "96"
  },
  {
    "question": "99 + 38 = ?",
    "options": ["141", "152", "155", "137"],
    "answer": "137"
  },
  {
    "question": "51 + 40 = ?",
    "options": ["95", "91", "106", "96"],
    "answer": "91"
  },
  {
    "question": "20 + 84 = ?",
    "options": ["104", "116", "115", "91"],
    "answer": "104"
  },
  {
    "question": "49 + 39 = ?",
    "options": ["88", "92", "81", "70"],
    "answer": "88"
  },
  {
    "question": "92 + 98 = ?",
    "options": ["175", "203", "202", "190"],
    "answer": "190"
  },
  {
    "question": "30 + 76 = ?",
    "options": ["95", "106", "88", "122"],
    "answer": "106"
  },
  {
    "question": "17 + 43 = ?",
    "options": ["60", "66", "40", "78"],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "80 + 74 = ?",
    "options": ["154", "164", "161", "151"],
    "answer": "154"
  },
  {
    "question": "55 + 79 = ?",
    "options": ["154", "117", "137", "134"],
    "answer": "134"
  },
  {
    "question": "97 + 99 = ?",
    "options": ["196", "201", "184", "191"],
    "answer": "196"
  },
  {
    "question": "56 + 12 = ?",
    "options": ["68", "61", "51", "63"],
    "answer": "68"
  },
  {
    "question": "18 + 23 = ?",
    "options": ["52", "41", "53", "24"],
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "question": "64 + 12 = ?",
    "options": ["68", "95", "76", "91"],
    "answer": "76"
  },
  {
    "question": "19 + 21 = ?",
    "options": ["41", "40", "43", "26"],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "80 + 96 = ?",
    "options": ["158", "186", "176", "182"],
    "answer": "176"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 + 25 = ?",
    "options": ["52", "37", "29", "26"],
    "answer": "37"
  },
  {
    "question": "91 + 49 = ?",
    "options": ["127", "138", "140", "154"],
    "answer": "140"
  },
  {
    "question": "39 + 31 = ?",
    "options": ["70", "89", "85", "87"],
    "answer": "70"
  },
  {
    "question": "14 + 41 = ?",
    "options": ["55", "39", "46", "54"],
    "answer": "55"
  },
  {
    "question": "49 + 40 = ?",
    "options": ["76", "86", "89", "96"],
    "answer": "89"
  },
  {
    "question": "98 + 77 = ?",
    "options": ["191", "175", "177", "174"],
    "answer": "175"
  },
  {
    "question": "89 + 40 = ?",
    "options": ["136", "133", "146", "129"],
    "answer": "129"
  },
  {
    "question": "45 + 90 = ?",
    "options": ["135", "154", "146", "117"],
    "answer": "135"
  },
  {
    "question": "48 + 45 = ?",
    "options": ["93", "80", "77", "106"],
    "answer": "93"
  },
  {
    "question": "93 + 27 = ?",
    "options": ["120", "135", "115", "108"],
    "answer": "120"
  },
  {
    "question": "18 + 39 = ?",
    "options": ["57", "38", "66", "46"],
    "answer": "57"
  },
  {
    "question": "81 + 94 = ?",
    "options": ["175", "194", "172", "178"],
    "answer": "175"
  },
  {
    "question": "50 + 23 = ?",
    "options": ["89", "85", "65", "73"],
    "answer": "73"
  },
  {
    "question": "21 + 33 = ?",
    "options": ["64", "72", "52", "54"],
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "63 + 86 = ?",
    "options": ["149", "166", "139", "142"],
    "answer": "149"
  },
  {
    "question": "43 + 80 = ?",
    "options": ["137", "125", "103", "123"],
    "answer": "123"
  },
  {
    "question": "87 + 44 = ?",
    "options": ["131", "130", "117", "136"],
    "answer": "131"
  },
  {
    "question": "39 + 62 = ?",
    "options": ["81", "116", "101", "87"],
    "answer": "101"
  },
  {
    "question": "51 + 88 = ?",
    "options": ["140", "139", "133", "157"],
    "answer": "139"
  },
  {
    "question": "95 + 84 = ?",
    "options": ["172", "179", "173", "199"],
    "answer": "179"
  },
  {
    "question": "706 + 769 = ?",
    "options": ["1474", "1491", "1471", "1475"],
    "answer": "1475"
  },
  {
    "question": "350 + 207 = ?",
    "options": ["555", "537", "548", "557"],
    "answer": "557"
  },
  {
    "question": "771 + 485 = ?",
    "options": ["1276", "1256", "1259", "1249"],
    "answer": "1256"
  },
  {
    "question": "442 + 123 = ?",
    "options": ["582", "565", "546", "570"],
    "answer": "565"
  },
  {
    "question": "732 + 914 = ?",
    "options": ["1632", "1660", "1646", "1644"],
    "answer": "1646"
  },
  {
    "question": "560 + 685 = ?",
    "options": ["1225", "1260", "1245", "1250"],
    "answer": "1245"
  },
  {
    "question": "383 + 114 = ?",
    "options": ["497", "487", "508", "486"],
    "answer": "497"
  },
  {
    "question": "707 + 724 = ?",
    "options": ["1431", "1420", "1433", "1451"],
    "answer": "1431"
  },
  {
    "question": "390 + 267 = ?",
    "options": ["670", "640", "657", "652"],
    "answer": "657"
  },
  {
    "question": "622 + 214 = ?",
    "options": ["821", "843", "846", "836"],
    "answer": "836"
  },
  {
    "question": "232 + 304 = ?",
    "options": ["545", "536", "544", "519"],
    "answer": "536"
  },
  {
    "question": "129 + 642 = ?",
    "options": ["778", "782", "771", "762"],
    "answer": "771"
  },
  {
    "question": "446 + 171 = ?",
    "options": ["617", "599", "616", "601"],
    "answer": "617"
  },
  {
    "question": "411 + 802 = ?",
    "options": ["1230", "1231", "1201", "1213"],
    "answer": "1213"
  },
  {
    "question": "604 + 520 = ?",
    "options": ["1130", "1127", "1124", "1108"],
    "answer": "1124"
  },
  {
    "question": "283 + 128 = ?",
    "options": ["401", "414", "411", "394"],
    "answer": "411"
  },
  {
    "question": "130 + 672 = ?",
    "options": ["796", "815", "782", "802"],
    "answer": "802"
  },
  {
    "question": "842 + 932 = ?",
    "options": ["1764", "1757", "1774", "1780"],
    "answer": "1774"
  },
  {
    "question": "732 + 223 = ?",
    "options": ["937", "955", "936", "969"],
    "answer": "955"
  },
  {
    "question": "541 + 559 = ?",
    "options": ["1100", "1081", "1080", "1082"],
    "answer": "1100"
  },
  {
    "question": "992 + 689 = ?",
    "options": ["1666", "1662", "1695", "1681"],
    "answer": "1681"
  },
  {
    "question": "910 + 135 = ?",
    "options": ["1027", "1049", "1046", "1045"],
    "answer": "1045"
  },
  {
    "question": "820 + 973 = ?",
    "options": ["1783", "1789", "1785", "1793"],
    "answer": "1793"
  },
  {
    "question": "748 + 851 = ?",
    "options": ["1591", "1593", "1599", "1619"],
    "answer": "1599"
  },
  {
    "question": "863 + 604 = ?",
    "options": ["1448", "1467", "1483", "1452"],
    "answer": "1467"
  },
  {
    "question": "360 + 589 = ?",
    "options": ["937", "961", "942", "949"],
    "answer": "949"
  },
  {
    "question": "852 + 112 = ?",
    "options": ["958", "951", "972", "964"],
    "answer": "964"
  },
  {
    "question": "203 + 125 = ?",
    "options": ["320", "316", "309", "328"],
    "answer": "328"
  },
  {
    "question": "759 + 739 = ?",
    "options": ["1513", "1498", "1508", "1483"],
    "answer": "1498"
  },
  {
    "question": "697 + 450 = ?",
    "options": ["1133", "1132", "1163", "1147"],
    "answer": "1147"
  },
  {
    "question": "900 + 476 = ?",
    "options": ["1389", "1376", "1394", "1367"],
    "answer": "1376"
  },
  {
    "question": "977 + 931 = ?",
    "options": ["1910", "1917", "1921", "1908"],
    "answer": "1908"
  },
  {
    "question": "916 + 254 = ?",
    "options": ["1166", "1150", "1154", "1170"],
    "answer": "1170"
  },
  {
    "question": "934 + 280 = ?",
    "options": ["1198", "1214", "1204", "1233"],
    "answer": "1214"
  },
  {
    "question": "651 + 726 = ?",
    "options": ["1383", "1382", "1386", "1377"],
    "answer": "1377"
  },
  {
    "question": "456 + 842 = ?",
    "options": ["1294", "1295", "1307", "1298"],
    "answer": "1298"
  },
  {
    "question": "978 + 417 = ?",
    "options": ["1395", "1401", "1386", "1406"],
    "answer": "1395"
  },
  {
    "question": "909 + 628 = ?",
    "options": ["1537", "1526", "1539", "1532"],
    "answer": "1537"
  },
  {
    "question": "105 + 610 = ?",
    "options": ["715", "705", "695", "724"],
    "answer": "715"
  },
  {
    "question": "612 + 708 = ?",
    "options": ["1338", "1326", "1320", "1318"],
    "answer": "1320"
  },
  {
    "question": "843 + 858 = ?",
    "options": ["1701", "1711", "1709", "1704"],
    "answer": "1701"
  },
  {
    "question": "363 + 414 = ?",
    "options": ["777", "766", "760", "773"],
    "answer": "777"
  },
  {
    "question": "571 + 150 = ?",
    "options": ["707", "721", "731", "702"],
    "answer": "721"
  },
  {
    "question": "622 + 273 = ?",
    "options": ["909", "898", "895", "881"],
    "answer": "895"
  },
  {
    "question": "773 + 461 = ?",
    "options": ["1238", "1241", "1234", "1251"],
    "answer": "1234"
  },
  {
    "question": "586 + 219 = ?",
    "options": ["805", "788", "804", "818"],
    "answer": "805"
  },
  {
    "question": "807 + 459 = ?",
    "options": ["1275", "1262", "1266", "1259"],
    "answer": "1266"
  },
  {
    "question": "632 + 623 = ?",
    "options": ["1255", "1270", "1267", "1272"],
    "answer": "1255"
  },
  {
    "question": "597 + 879 = ?",
    "options": ["1495", "1476", "1470", "1468"],
    "answer": "1476"
  },
  {
    "question": "783 + 583 = ?",
    "options": ["1360", "1366", "1376", "1372"],
    "answer": "1366"
  },
  {
    "question": "6346 + 5604 = ?",
    "options": ["11950", "11931", "11944", "11966"],
    "answer": "11950"
  },
  {
    "question": "2048 + 4578 = ?",
    "options": ["6616", "6644", "6621", "6626"],
    "answer": "6626"
  },
  {
    "question": "1085 + 7144 = ?",
    "options": ["8234", "8229", "8209", "8231"],
    "answer": "8229"
  },
  {
    "question": "6436 + 2420 = ?",
    "options": ["8856", "8858", "8874", "8855"],
    "answer": "8856"
  },
  {
    "question": "2311 + 4934 = ?",
    "options": ["7260", "7245", "7225", "7232"],
    "answer": "7245"
  },
  {
    "question": "7595 + 7780 = ?",
    "options": ["15375", "15376", "15356", "15389"],
    "answer": "15375"
  },
  {
    "question": "5308 + 2211 = ?",
    "options": ["7519", "7531", "7530", "7527"],
    "answer": "7519"
  },
  {
    "question": "7797 + 6864 = ?",
    "options": ["14670", "14659", "14677", "14661"],
    "answer": "14661"
  },
  {
    "question": "1559 + 9679 = ?",
    "options": ["11237", "11238", "11250", "11225"],
    "answer": "11238"
  },
  {
    "question": "4032 + 8527 = ?",
    "options": ["12558", "12566", "12557", "12559"],
    "answer": "12559"
  },
  {
    "question": "5499 + 8132 = ?",
    "options": ["13631", "13635", "13630", "13641"],
    "answer": "13631"
  },
  {
    "question": "9113 + 1712 = ?",
    "options": ["10835", "10825", "10841", "10831"],
    "answer": "10825"
  },
  {
    "question": "6121 + 9723 = ?",
    "options": ["15852", "15844", "15835", "15827"],
    "answer": "15844"
  },
  {
    "question": "8868 + 8893 = ?",
    "options": ["17777", "17742", "17757", "17761"],
    "answer": "17761"
  },
  {
    "question": "3537 + 6401 = ?",
    "options": ["9932", "9924", "9953", "9938"],
    "answer": "9938"
  },
  {
    "question": "5163 + 4046 = ?",
    "options": ["9199", "9223", "9201", "9209"],
    "answer": "9209"
  },
  {
    "question": "4154 + 9037 = ?",
    "options": ["13185", "13191", "13179", "13195"],
    "answer": "13191"
  },
  {
    "question": "8163 + 3068 = ?",
    "options": ["11238", "11246", "11231", "11250"],
    "answer": "11231"
  },
  {
    "question": "5360 + 5932 = ?",
    "options": ["11298", "11292", "11290", "11294"],
    "answer": "11292"
  },
  {
    "question": "5217 + 3809 = ?",
    "options": ["9026", "9016", "9006", "9029"],
    "answer": "9026"
  },
  {
    "question": "5541 + 5107 = ?",
    "options": ["10668", "10648", "10651", "10654"],
    "answer": "10648"
  },
  {
    "question": "1070 + 2245 = ?",
    "options": ["3315", "3321", "3327", "3309"],
    "answer": "3315"
  },
  {
    "question": "7099 + 7840 = ?",
    "options": ["14938", "14925", "14939", "14933"],
    "answer": "14939"
  },
  {
    "question": "4303 + 4670 = ?",
    "options": ["8977", "8990", "8973", "8980"],
    "answer": "8973"
  },
  {
    "question": "7379 + 1957 = ?",
    "options": ["9339", "9335", "9318", "9336"],
    "answer": "9336"
  },
  {
    "question": "9709 + 3961 = ?",
    "options": ["13671", "13670", "13661", "13657"],
    "answer": "13670"
  },
  {
    "question": "3460 + 7313 = ?",
    "options": ["10765", "10782", "10775", "10773"],
    "answer": "10773"
  },
  {
    "question": "6722 + 3428 = ?",
    "options": ["10138", "10133", "10158", "10150"],
    "answer": "10150"
  },
  {
    "question": "9515 + 2155 = ?",
    "options": ["11665", "11670", "11655", "11659"],
    "answer": "11670"
  },
  {
    "question": "8570 + 7103 = ?",
    "options": ["15673", "15693", "15684", "15680"],
    "answer": "15673"
  },
  {
    "question": "6607 + 7552 = ?",
    "options": ["14169", "14158", "14140", "14159"],
    "answer": "14159"
  },
  {
    "question": "3945 + 1373 = ?",
    "options": ["5323", "5300", "5334", "5318"],
    "answer": "5318"
  },
  {
    "question": "1126 + 7944 = ?",
    "options": ["9070", "9082", "9084", "9063"],
    "answer": "9070"
  },
  {
    "question": "7370 + 7705 = ?",
    "options": ["15075", "15084", "15064", "15063"],
    "answer": "15075"
  },
  {
    "question": "2919 + 5190 = ?",
    "options": ["8109", "8089", "8098", "8101"],
    "answer": "8109"
  },
  {
    "question": "7934 + 6380 = ?",
    "options": ["14308", "14314", "14332", "14311"],
    "answer": "14314"
  },
  {
    "question": "4132 + 7050 = ?",
    "options": ["11189", "11179", "11182", "11197"],
    "answer": "11182"
  },
  {
    "question": "2690 + 8554 = ?",
    "options": ["11258", "11243", "11249", "11244"],
    "answer": "11244"
  },
  {
    "question": "2664 + 7500 = ?",
    "options": ["10164", "10177", "10165", "10145"],
    "answer": "10164"
  },
  {
    "question": "9790 + 1733 = ?",
    "options": ["11530", "11543", "11526", "11523"],
    "answer": "11523"
  },
  {
    "question": "7778 + 2913 = ?",
    "options": ["10679", "10682", "10672", "10691"],
    "answer": "10691"
  },
  {
    "question": "8864 + 9464 = ?",
    "options": ["18310", "18320", "18328", "18336"],
    "answer": "18328"
  },
  {
    "question": "4673 + 7206 = ?",
    "options": ["11883", "11865", "11878", "11879"],
    "answer": "11879"
  },
  {
    "question": "3197 + 1234 = ?",
    "options": ["4422", "4445", "4431", "4437"],
    "answer": "4431"
  },
  {
    "question": "2048 + 4283 = ?",
    "options": ["6312", "6331", "6339", "6345"],
    "answer": "6331"
  },
  {
    "question": "6624 + 3173 = ?",
    "options": ["9816", "9806", "9797", "9777"],
    "answer": "9797"
  },
  {
    "question": "1054 + 6298 = ?",
    "options": ["7359", "7352", "7339", "7370"],
    "answer": "7352"
  },
  {
    "question": "2867 + 7122 = ?",
    "options": ["9988", "10009", "9989", "10007"],
    "answer": "9989"
  },
  {
    "question": "1551 + 1678 = ?",
    "options": ["3231", "3232", "3219", "3229"],
    "answer": "3229"
  },
  {
    "question": "5489 + 9193 = ?",
    "options": ["14672", "14682", "14699", "14688"],
    "answer": "14682"
  },
];

export default level10questions;